{
    "id": "9acb90426f804c6e894207f45cac78f4",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She would never …………….. if she hadn’t changed jobs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have been promoted",
                "has been promoted",
                "have promoted",
                "has promoted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7358e7f9bccc41f8a442356d361f2a67"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have no interest in politics. I never had, and I ………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will never",
                "never will",
                "never does",
                "never would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "33ec9e1328484f49833e40e852a43ea6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am going to do my homework, and ………………. I am going to play.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "afterwards",
                "after",
                "afterward",
                "later"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "171ea7cb95c1448abcc66bf25442a971"
        },
        {
            "question": "I expected to pass the exam, but I failed ……………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finally",
                "at all",
                "after all",
                "nevertheless"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dfafb928328e4ec195c11100799ec97d"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I was ……………… I was working.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at your age",
                "your age",
                "of your age",
                "at the age of you"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8065bea9ca5b441e843e1ed9d7d0e6fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I had known that she was coming, I ………………. the function in the first place.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wouldn't attend",
                "wouldn't have attended",
                "won't have attended"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "43a23918561749daa1f0ed147c9f6ca8"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………. she informed the police, she wouldn’t have been in trouble now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Had",
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8bb21a5602354230b318ebad50d56c42"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know where they ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have gone",
                "had gone",
                "would go"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fc4f57d76b1145498b7ff99c851fbe9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I hadn’t lost consciousness, I ………………… out what they were doing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "could find",
                "could have found",
                "can find"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4bf25775c3354765a649ee4a207afcee"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………… this to him. He is really upset.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should not do",
                "should not have done",
                "shall not do"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8ac98c6d32244391a2b5818ed9b47f54"
        }
    ]
}